romancestuck.com 2011-06-23

# RomanceStuck Privacy Policy

**You are here:[Home](http://www.romancestuck.com/) > Privacy Policy**

To protect your privacy, **RomanceStuck** has instituted policies that give you information and control.

**RomanceStuck** does not collect any personal information from any visitor when they arrive on the **RomanceStuck** site.

**RomanceStuck** requires an email address and name from those wishing to subscribe to the periodic newsletter. This information is only used to send the periodic newsletter. **RomanceStuck** will offer the option of unsubscribing from the newsletter in every issue that is sent out.

**RomanceStuck** offers a 'refer-a-friend' service that requires a user to submit their email address and those of their friends to whom they are recommending the site. **RomanceStuck** only uses this information to send the 'refer-a-friend' email at the time that the form is filled out.

**RomanceStuck** requires email addresses, names, and other submission information from those users who choose to submit their romance ideas, tips and/or articles for inclusion in **RomanceStuck's** database. The email address is used only used to contact the user in regards to their site submission and will not be used in any other manner. Other submitted data will appear on the appropriate page within **RomanceStuck.com**. All users submitting ideas, tips, and/or articles must agree to the [submission terms](http://www.romancestuck.com/submit-rules.htm).

**RomanceStuck** requires an email address, name, and website information from those webmasters who choose to submit their romance related web site for addition into **RomanceStuck's** Romance Directory. This information is used only used to contact the webmaster in regards to their site submission.

**RomanceStuck** requires email addresses, names, and other personal information from those users who choose to subscribe to the **RomanceStuck** forums. This information is used only to contact the subscriber regarding their forum subscription and situations relating to their subscription. This information will not be used in any other manner.

**RomanceStuck** requires a name and location for all users who submit a comment on the site. Additionally, we collect the IP address, date, and time as related to your submission for tracking purposes.

**RomanceStuck** is a free site supported by advertising. We run various third party ads that may place and/or read cookies on your browser or use web beacons to collect information in the course of the ads being served on our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). Additionally, within your browser you can manage all cookie acceptance, allowing you to turn off cookies, accept session only coolies, or delete cookies. For detailed information, view your browser's help menu. For more information on how to opt out of cookies, please visit [WorldPrivacyForum.org](http://www.worldprivacyforum.org/cookieoptout.html).

For specific privacy policies for other **RomanceStuck** services offered via other companies (either advertised, affiliated, or other), please visit the individual company websites.

**UNDER NO CIRCUMSTANCES WILL ROMANCESTUCK SHARE YOUR EMAIL ADDRESS WITH A THIRD PARTY.**

If you have any questions, about this privacy statement, our online practices, or your dealings with our web sites, you can contact: [webmaster@romancestuck.com](http://www.romancestuck.com/contactus.php)

Subscribe & Share:

---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---  
  
To link to this page, copy the following code to your site:
